A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1991
Library of Virginia
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 24, Roscher, Derrick (Box 7, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 24, Ruggiero, Louis (Box 7, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 24, Johnson, Demetrius D. (Box 7, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 24, Graham, George Jett (Box 7, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 26, Knight, Robert Weldon AKA R. W. Knight AKA Will Knight (Box 7, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 26, Childs, Johnnie Lee (Box 7, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 29, Inn, Lat (Box 7, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 July 29, Lambert, Loretta Lynne (Box 7, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 July 5, Bishop, Larry Davis (Box 7, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 July 5, Fox, Sheree Lynn Forman (Box 7, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 July 9, Edwards, James (Box 7, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 July 24, Hague, Doris Elizabeth AKA Doris Elizabeth Watts (Box 7, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 July 24, Hodge, Teresa Gaye (Box 7, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 5, Harris, Gregory B. (Box 7, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 5, Thomas, Tyrone AKA Tyrone Shakees Thomas AKA Tony Thomas (Box 7, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 5, Smith, James (Box 7, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 5, Noll, Kevin (Box 7, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 5, Hafner, Michael David (Box 7, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 7, Jones, James Allen (Box 7, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 7, Rogers, Bobby Dean (Box 7, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 14, Perry, Lydia AKA Wanda Hood (Box 7, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 August 27, Loyd, William Lee (Box 7, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1991 August-September (Box 8, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 7, Wilkerson, Raymond Lee (Box 8, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 7, Hawkins, Alfred, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 7, Gorman, John Joseph (Box 8, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 14, Sauer, Barbara (Box 8, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 16, Pearson, Gregory Dane (Box 8, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 16, Moore, Kevin (Box 8, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 20, Vest, James Edward (Box 8, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 August 20, Johnson, Larry C. AKA Eddie Johnson (Box 8, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Burrell, Kevin McClung (Box 8, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Collins, Daniel James, Sr. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Davis, Pamela Kay (Box 8, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Farrow, Thomas Hamilton (Box 8, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Gentry, John Thomas (Box 8, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Hunter, Edward Nathaniel (Box 8, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Paige, Daniel Lee (Box 8, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 6, Webber, James Allen (Box 8, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 August 7, Zimmerman, John Paul (Box 8, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 9, Bjorkstrom, James Keith (Box 8, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 10, Payne, Darrell Kent (Box 8, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 13, Dial, Michael Grant (Box 8, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 10, Ross, Robert Wayne (Box 8, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 18, Stultz, Sterling Eugene (Box 8, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 18, Turner, Marie (Box 8, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 18, Thompson, Jason, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 24, Burton, Mark Wayne (Box 8, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 24, Taylor, Leroy (Box 8, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 25, Trivett, Donald (Box 8, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 25, Rader, Richard Evan (Box 8, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 25, Milne, Stephen Maxwell (Box 8, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 25, Watson, Shirley Jean AKA Shirley Batts (Box 8, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 27, Salyers, Gary Carter (Box 8, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 September 30, Coleman, George M. (Box 8, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Young, James C. (Box 8, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Johnson, Harold Anthony (Box 8, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Cutlip, Margaret Ann AKA Margaret Ann Briganti AKA Margaret Ann West AKA Margaret Ann Webb (Box 8, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Coleman, Bobby Lee (Box 8, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Stinson, Frank Charles (Box 8, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Nichols, Jeff Allen (Box 8, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 4, Disario, Paschal (Box 8, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Magnusson, Joseph Paul, Sr. (Box 8, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Gorbey, Michael Steven (Box 8, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Denny, William Monroe (Box 8, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Hoffman, Mark David (Box 8, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Shepherd, Patrick Lee (Box 8, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Thompson, Joe Allen (Box 8, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 5, Willey, Robert Edgar (Box 8, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 12, England, Ricky (NMN) (Box 8, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 12, McDermott, Clive Anthony (Box 8, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 12, Vernon, Robert Joseph (Box 8, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 12, Ratliff, Diana (Box 8, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 12, Harlow, James Delton AKA Henry Paul Jenkins (Box 8, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Cromeenes,Darryl Jean AKA James Thomas Cassell (Box 8, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 20, Smith, Oliver S. (Box 8, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Longoria, Michael J. (Box 8, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Frassrand, George Willis (Box 8, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Thomas, Edward (Box 8, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Bowser, Daniel Wayne (Box 8, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Diluzio, Nicholas (Box 8, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 September 27, Beard, Landrum Jeffrey AKA Jeffrey Landrum Beard (Box 8, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1991 September-November (Box 9, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Robert A. Pino (Box 9, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Boyce, Cecil William Kelly, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Bullock, David Warren (Box 9, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Thomas Alan Davidson AKA Thomas Allen Davidson (Box 9, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Hutchind, Peter (Box 9, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Lipford, Grayson Bernard, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Overstreet, Travis Wayne (Box 9, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Powers, Dennis Darrell (Box 9, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Shafer, George W. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Shawn, William E. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Simmons, Michael Paul (Box 9, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 September 9, Warner, Cameron Elwood, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 11, Scott, Gale Montrelia (Box 9, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 11, Williams, James AKA Keith Williams (Box 9, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 16, Frick, Christine M. Healy (Box 9, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 16, Carter, Vaughn Desmond AKA Desi Walker AKA Carter AKA Desi Carter (Box 9, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 11, Dehoney, Michael Forbes (Box 9, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 25, McElhaney, George (Box 9, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 October 28, Montero, Julio John (Box 9, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 4, King, William Mark (Box 9, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 February 22, Dobbs, David Warren AKA David Dobbs (Box 9, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 4, Grohman, Michael Richard (Box 9, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 4, Vawter, Mark Steven (Box 9, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 4, Brill, Christopher Michael (Box 9, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 21, Trell, Donald (Box 9, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 October 25, Artis, Reginald (Box 9, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Branham, Kathy Lynn Debord (Box 9, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Carter, Carroll Paul, Sr. (Box 9, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Carter, Shirley May (Box 9, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Crutchfield, Milton Clinton (Box 9, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Dooley, Hilton Swanson (Box 9, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Fadool, Yolanda Mills (Box 9, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Jones, John Thomas, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, O'Reilly, Linda Kay (Box 9, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Owens, Ronald Gene (Box 9, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Palmer, Diane Lynn AKA Diane Lynn (Box 9, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Pickens, Jimmy Aggie, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Plybon, Howard Edward (Box 9, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Short, Russell Lewis (Box 9, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Slater, Richard Paul, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Smith, Roger Lee (Box 9, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Tucker, Sandra Eva AKA Sandra Eva Mitchell (Box 9, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Unser, Edward Francis, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 11, McClure, Charles Preston (Box 9, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 31, Smith, Letitia Retina (Box 9, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 October 1, Williams, Donald Allison (Box 9, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Absolute Pardon, 1991 November 11, Worsham, Welton Earl (Box 9, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Clark, Larry Audrea AKA Larry Andrea Clark (Box 9, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Wiggins, Susan Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Shelton, Monty Earl (Box 9, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Fernandez, Luis Felepe, III (Box 9, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Wiggins, William Joseph (Box 9, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Moone, Alvin W. (Box 9, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Mixon, Thomas Dean, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Garnitz, Daniel Seth (Box 9, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Calhoun, Randall (Box 9, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Baker, Tommy Lee (Box 9, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Martinez, Francisco (Box 9, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 13, Amayo, Emanuel (Box 9, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 14, Hairston, Howard Burnett (Box 9, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 14, Holland, George Wilbur (Box 9, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 15, Mason, William H. (Box 9, Folder 63)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 1, Nole, Brian David (Box 9, Folder 64)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 19, Hansen, Ronald Lee, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 65)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 20, Harris, Michael Edmond (Box 9, Folder 66)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 20, Beck, Riad (Box 9, Folder 67)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 25, Dillard, James Elizze (Box 9, Folder 68)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 25, Williamson, Lawrence Rolen (Box 9, Folder 69)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 25, Batiste, Edward, Jr. (Box 9, Folder 70)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 November 25, Turner, Marie Suzanne (Box 9, Folder 71)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1991 November-December (Box 10, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Shields, Major AKA Michael Bailey (Box 10, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Edwards, Keith Brian (Box 10, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Rinaldi, Nicholas Eugene (Box 10, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Sizemore, Terry Ira (Box 10, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Tamir, Muhammad T. (Box 10, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Lovin, Donald E. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Shaw-Taylor, Attu Apeatsi (Box 10, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 5, Junta, James J. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 18, Hairston, Charlie G. AKA Charles Greeley Hairston (Box 10, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Hendricks, Jerry Lee (Box 10, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Stocks, Shean Remaro (Box 10, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Hylton, Teddy Lee (Box 10, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Hurn, James (Box 10, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Hampton, David Lloyd (Box 10, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Beachman, Johnny L. (Box 10, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Newsome, Willard D. (Box 10, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Patrick, Donald L. (Box 10, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Monroe, Kirk D. (Box 10, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Green, Garland (Box 10, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, King, Frederick Douglas, Sr. (Box 10, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Walker, James Lawrence (Box 10, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 19, Said, Hani A. AKA Alsaid Hani (Box 10, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Beeson, Deborah Ellen AKA Debra Beeson AKA Debra Harris (Box 10, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Winston, Gerald K. (Box 10, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Swain, George Alton (Box 10, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Takach, Steven Andrew (Box 10, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 November 25, Holland, Brian Keith (Box 10, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Brown, Jerry Thomas (Box 10, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Hall, Carol (Box 10, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Hicks, James Robert (Box 10, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Hill, Alfred Wilson (Box 10, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Izon, Oliver Leroy (Box 10, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Janeka, Dianna Davis (Box 10, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Jones, John Henry, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Jones, Tommy Julian (Box 10, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Kearney, Louis Alonzo (Box 10, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Mason, Winifred I. (Box 10, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Perry, Michele Angela (Box 10, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Pritt, William Massie (Box 10, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 18, Southwood, Jeffrey Lynn AKA Jeffrey Lynn Carlson (Box 10, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 20, Dancy, Laurence Edward (Box 10, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 20, Oxenreider,Robert George (Box 10, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 November 20, Vaughan, Carlton Wade (Box 10, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 9, Amos, Pamela Kim (Box 10, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 9, Hoffman, Gene (Box 10, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Pearson, Keith (Box 10, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Johnson, Sterling Alfred, Jr. (Box 10, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Cooper, Kenneth (Box 10, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Payne, Doris Marie (Box 10, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Johnson, Rebecca M. (Box 10, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Stewart, David Lee (Box 10, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Cameron, Milton (Box 10, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Fincher, Anthony J. AKA James Elwood Fincher (Box 10, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Swint, John Joseph (Box 10, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 16, Phillips, Jean M. (Box 10, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 17, Wise, Larry Wayne (Box 10, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 23, Brownlee, David C., Jr. (Box 10, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 24, Cooper, Vanessa N. (Box 10, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 31, Stevens, Wayne Edward AKA Edward Wayne Stevens (Box 10, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 31, Robinette, David Summer (Box 10, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 31, Butt, Noel Anthony AKA Nowell Anthony Burr (Box 10, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1991 December 31, Falin, Dallas Cecil (Box 10, Folder 63)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 2, Vesley, Daniel Lee AKA Daniel Lee Butterworth (Box 10, Folder 64)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 2, Whittiker, Terry Lee (Box 10, Folder 65)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 2, Jones, Kevin Dwayne (Box 10, Folder 66)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 2, Tyspinger, Johney B. AKA Bobby Joe Spurrier AKA Johnny B. Tysinger (Box 10, Folder 67)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Parry, Thomas (Box 10, Folder 68)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 5, Dykes, Michael Anthony (Box 10, Folder 69)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 9, Long, Richard D. AKA Richard Dean Long (Box 10, Folder 70)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 9, Reid, Gino L. (Box 10, Folder 71)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 17, Squires, Samantha (Box 10, Folder 72)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Henry, John Francis, III (Box 10, Folder 73)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Wilcox, Winston Parks (Box 10, Folder 74)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Kyger, Sylvester (Box 10, Folder 75)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Slade, James Howard (Box 10, Folder 76)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Hancock, Joseph Allen (Box 10, Folder 77)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Bennett, Willis A. (Box 10, Folder 78)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Fraher, Elizabeth S. (Box 10, Folder 79)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 23, Daza, Edgar I. (Box 10, Folder 80)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1991 December 30, Romero, Miguel (Box 10, Folder 81)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Austin, Chester Roy (Box 10, Folder 82)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Fletcher, James Wallace Jackson, III (Box 10, Folder 83)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Hagwood, Curtis (Box 10, Folder 84)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Kennon, Ronnie Edward (Box 10, Folder 85)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Mundie, Paul Jeffrey (Box 10, Folder 86)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Saunders, Charles William (Box 10, Folder 87)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Settle, Elwood (Box 10, Folder 88)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Shumate, George Carson (Box 10, Folder 89)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Spence, Michael Wayne (Box 10, Folder 90)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1991 December 31, Ward, David Allen (Box 10, Folder 91)